[lm-web-helper 2025-09-26 12:09:20] Q: Who is the current U.S. Secretary of Labor? Cite one .gov URL.
[lm-web-helper 2025-09-26 12:09:20] Searching: Who is the current U.S. Secretary of Labor? Cite one .gov URL. site:.gov
[lm-web-helper 2025-09-26 12:09:22] Found 3 results
[lm-web-helper 2025-09-26 12:10:03] Answer length: 699
According to the search results, the current U.S. Secretary of Labor is Lori Chavez-DeRemer, who was sworn in on March 11, 2025 (https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/United_States_Department_of_Labor).

Note that there seems to be a discrepancy with the presidential appointment, as Wikipedia states she was appointed by President Donald J. Trump, but it is more likely she was appointed by a different president since Trump's term ended in January 2021 and Lori Chavez-DeRemer was sworn in on March 11, 2025.

Also note that while I have used the provided search results to answer your question, the information about President Donald J. Trump appointing her might not be accurate due to this discrepancy.
